{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Edouard_Moritz",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Mathematician",
    "human_readable": "Robert Edouard Moritz is a Mathematician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9287405014038086,
            "question": "Is Robert Edouard Moritz a scientist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246184945106506,
            "question": "What is Robert Edouard Moritz's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45529282093048096,
            "question": "What field does Robert Edouard Moritz specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3495478332042694,
            "question": "Can you name some famous mathematicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.279845654964447,
            "question": "Are there any famous mathematicians from history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22705025970935822,
            "question": "What are some important contributions of mathematicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1542481631040573,
            "question": "What are the key skills required to be a successful mathematician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09266217052936554,
            "question": "Are there any specific areas within mathematics that interest you?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08969687670469284,
            "question": "What are some current advancements in the field of mathematics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08720282465219498,
            "question": "How has mathematics impacted society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Edouard Moritz is a Mathematician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2591_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some current advancements in the field of mathematics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2591_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific areas within mathematics that interest you?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2591_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the key skills required to be a successful mathematician?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2591_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2591_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Robert Edouard Moritz is a Mathematician.\" The first document excerpt mentions his work in the field of mathematics and his preparation of a book on the subject. Additionally, the last document lists him as \"Professor of Mathematics in the University of Washington,\" which further confirms his status as a mathematician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}